<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<!-- Bosses string set template:
    Boss Title(Optional or Not):
    Boss Description:
    Boss Lore:
    Boss fight strategy:
    Loot: -->

<resources>

    <!-- String Array for Boss list Activity -->
    <string-array name="boss_list">
        <item>Amygdala</item>
        <item>Blood Starved Beast</item>
        <item>Celestial Emissary</item>
        <item>Cleric Beast</item>
        <item>Darkbeast Paarl</item>
        <item>Ebrietas, Daughter of the Cosmos</item>
        <item>Father Gascoigne</item>
        <item>Gehrman, The Old Hunter</item>
        <item>Martyr Logarius</item>
        <item>Mergo\'s Wet Nurse</item>
        <item>Micolash, Host of the Nightmare</item>
        <item>Moon Presence</item>
        <item>One Reborn</item>
        <item>Rom, the Vacuous Spider</item>
        <item>Shadows of Yharnam</item>
        <item>Vicar Amelia</item>
        <item>Witch of Hemwick</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Amygdala -->
    <string name="amygdala">Amygdala</string>
    <string name="amygdala_description">Amygdala is one of the Great Ones that the Hunter will hear
    about often if they are listening to the lore in Yharnam. This being has many arms, and can be
    found all over Yharnam once the Hunter has gained enough insight.</string>
    <string name="amygdala_lore">Amygdala seems to be one of the \"true\" Great Ones as it is shaped
    much like the Moon Presence. This shows that this being is not a construction of the Great Ones,
    nor is it one of the experiments that created a Great One done by man. Amygdala appears to be
    quite powerful, yet rather simple. The being is capable of rending holes in reality, camouflaging
    itself from lesser beings, and creating copies of itself to keep an eye on many locations at once.
    This being is named after a part of the human brain called the Amygdala, which is central to human
    kind\'s ability to emotional reactions, decision making, and memory hinting at this being\'s
    purpose for being in Yharnam.</string>
    <string name="amygdala_fight_strategy">Amygdala is weak to Arcane, Fire and Bolt damage; however
    that is only if the Hunter is striking in the right spots. It will become quickly evident that this
    being\'s weak spots are it\'s arms, and it\'s head. This maes the fight a little more risky as
    the Hunter will have to keep themselves in, or close to Amygdala\'s areas of attack. Keeping off
    to the side, and staying closer to the front is the safest place to be for this fight, and keep
    in mind, if Amygdala jumps, it won\'t do damage if you stay still. This is a tough fight once
    Amygdala reaches approx. 30% of it\'s HP, just remember to stay off to the side and near the front
    of this being until an opening appears to strike.</string>
    <string name="amygdala_loot">Amygdala awards the Hunter with three insight for discovering it,
    and three more for killing it. Also drops blood echoes and an Ailing Loran Chalice.</string>

    <!-- Blood Starved Beast -->
    <string name="boss_blood_starved_beast">Blood Starved Beast</string>
    <string name="blood_starved_beast_description">The Blood Starved Beast in an optional boss that
    the Hunter may come across on their journey. It is located in a run down church in Old Yharnam.
    This beast has a grotesque figure with an elongated torso, with all of the skin ripped from it\'s
    back. It wears a ragged cloth over it\'s head and shoulders, seemingly self conscious of it\'s looks.</string>
    <string name="blood_starved_beast_lore">This beast seems to be worshipped in Old Yharnam by
    the Beast Patients, as there is a Blood Starved Beast found crucified inside the Cathdedral
    located just after Djura\'s tower. Examining the altar in this room shows depictions of the Moon
    Presence, hinting at a connection between the Blood Staved Beast, and the Great One.</string>
    <string name="blood_starved_beast_fight_strategy">The Blood Starved Beast is a very, very quick
    opponent when attacking; however it takes it\'s time approaching the Hunter. It\'s attacks are
    capable of poisoning the Hunter, adding an additional level of caution to be taken when confronting
    this beast. One method for tackling this fight is to bring a flame sprayer, upgraded as much as
    possible and get very aggressive with the beast as it is incredibly weak to fire. Key times for
    peak aggression are when the best is switching into it\'s next phase. This will enable the Hunter
    to rack up their multiplier, roasting the beast before it gets much of a chance to fight at all.
    Another method that works well against this foe is to use Alfred as a shield. He can be summoned
    from just outside of the boss area and is fairly resilient(beware, he will likely die in the third
    phase, so be prepared for a fight no matter what if you use this method). The Blood Starved Beast
    has certain obvious attacks that can be parried, and countered with a visceral attack for easy
    damage.</string>
    <string name="blood_starved_beast_loot">The Blood Starved Beast drops blood echoes, a Pthumeru
    chalice, and one insight for defeating in.</string>

    <!-- Celestial Emissary -->
    <string name="celestial_emissary">Celestial Emissary</string>
    <string name="celestial_emissary_description">Celestial Emissary can be found in the Orphanage in
    the Upper Cathedral. To find this location the Hunter will need to traverse the Upper Cathedral
    Ward and find the Orphanage Key dropped by the Brainsucker through the door where the Wolf Beast
    jumps through the window at you. This boss is a giant version of the normal version of celestial
    emissaries, and is one of the easier fights in the game when encountered.</string>
    <string name="celestial_emissary_lore">As the Iosefka impostor experimented on survivors, she must
    have come across a survivor with extra strength, as this experiment is much tougher to kill than
    the rest of them. As the Hunter attacks, the Emissary\'s powers slowly awaken and come to
    fruition when the fight is coming to it\'s end.</string>
    <string name="celestial_emissary_fight_strategy">The Celestial Emissary is a pretty easy fight, as
    long as the Hunter has experience killing the regular emissaries. Upon finding this boss, the Hunter
    will have to figure out which emissary is the boss. After this the Hunter will need to work their
    way through the group of normal emissaries to attack the boss. The boss itself is weak to
    bolt at first, then weak to fire later in the fight. It is recommended to ignore the regular enemies
    as they will keep re-spawning while the boss remains alive. Once the boss gets to about 30% HP,
    it will grow in size and become a little more aggressive. Stay close to it at this point as it will
    unleash a cosmic barrage at the Hunter, which can end the fight quite quickly.</string>
    <string name="celestial_emissary_loot">Celestial Emissary rewards the Hunter with two insight for
    killing it, some blood echoes, and the Communion rune.</string>

    <!-- Cleric Beast -->
    <string name="boss_cleric_beast">Cleric Beast</string>
    <string name="cleric_beast_description">This beast has enormous, disfigured horns, body parts that
    are completely mismatched in size, and a horribly disfigured face. this beast can be found across
    the Great Bridge in central Yharnam and is the first optional boss that the Hunter will come across.</string>
    <string name="cleric_beast_lore">There is a small tidbit in Hunter scripture that states
    that the members of the Healing Church would eventually turn into the most horrible beasts. The
    Cleric Beast seems to be proof of this.</string>
    <string name="cleric_beast_fight_strategy">A common strategy for fighting this beast with no
    special preparation in mind is to dodge forward and to the left when the beast attacks, and get
    in behind it to avoid as much damage as possible. The beast only has one attack when the Hunter
    is in behind and if the Hunter is careful, they can dodge with the attack to remain behind the beast
    until it leaps away, or backs into a wall. Bringing molotov cocktails and a weapon tht deals
    serration damage is a good idea for this fight as the beast is weak to both types of damage.
    It is also possible to break the beasts legs after enough damage is done to it, allowing for a
    big window of opportunity to deal a large amount of damage.</string>
    <string name="cleric_beast_loot">The Cleric Beast drops some blood echoes, the Sword Hunter Badge,
    and three insight when defeated. Discovering this beast rewards the Hunter with one blood echo as
    well.</string>

    <!-- Darkbeast Paarl -->
    <string name="boss_darkbeast_paarl">Darkbeast Paarl</string>
    <string name="darkbeast_paarl_description">Darkbeast Paarl can be found in Hypogean Gaol, in a
    slightly secret area that can be found by finding the room with two witches and a couple Snatchers.
    Near the back of this room is a tunnel in the wall that leads to this bosses\' area. This beast
    is a deformed beast covered with lightning enhanced hair/aura that it will repeatedly activate
    throughout the fight.</string>
    <string name="darkbeast_paarl_lore"> It\'s face, if examined closely is very wrinkled, hinting
    that this beast is incredibly old and has been guarding this entrance to Old Yharnam for quite
    some time. </string>
    <string name="darkbeast_paarl_fight_strategy">Darkbeast Paarl is weak to fire and arcane damage,
    so bringing fire papers or an arcane weapon with help greatly with this fight. Using a combination
    of Oil Urns and Molotov cocktails to throw Paarl off balance, then crippling his legs, opening him
    up to a visceral attack is likely the easiest method for defeating this boss as it enables the Hunter
    to essentially stun lock him until he died. Getting underneath the boss is always recommended as
    the boss has a difficult time doing damage to the Hunter while they are under him.</string>
    <string name="darkbeast_paarl_loot">Darkbeast Paarl drops some blood echoes, a Spark Hunter Badge,
    and three insight when defeated. The Hunter is rewarded with one insight for discovering the boss.</string>

    <!-- Ebrietas, Daughter of the Cosmos -->
    <string name="ebrietas">Ebrietas, Daughter of the Cosmos</string>
    <string name="ebrietas_description">Ebrietas is a monstrosity of a Great One(see picture), and can
    be found after killing the Celestial Emissary. To find this boss, the Hunter must locate the
    breakable window in the Lumenflower Gardens, and take the elevator down to the Altar of Despair.</string>
    <string name="ebrietas_lore">The initial encounter with Ebrietas began the Yharnamite\'s interest
    in the cosmos from within the old labyrinth, leading to the establishment of the Choir. Delving
    deep into the labyrinth allowed the members of the Choir to discover, and bring back the Great
    Isz chalice, and have audience with Ebrietas.</string>
    <string name="ebrietas_fight_strategy">Though Ebrietas appears to be a large slug with tentacles,
    it is capable of incredibly fast turn speeds and sweeping attacks with huge range. This is a
    battle of attrition and there are few easy ways of ending this battle. Try to focus on attacking
    the chest of this being, as it will retaliate with much more predictable moves, allowing for an
    easier time defending/dodging the attacks. Ebrietas is weak to bolt damage, and it wouldn\'t
    hurt to bring runes/gems that give bonus dsmage vs. kin.</string>
    <string name="ebrietas_loot">Discovering Ebrietas will give the Hunter three insight. Killing her
    rewards the Hunter with three more insight, a hefty amount of blood echoes, and the Great Isz Chalice.</string>

    <!-- Father Gascoigne -->
    <string name="boss_father_gascoigne">Father Gascoigne</string>
    <string name="father_gascoigne_description">Father Gascoigne is the first mandatory boss in
    Bloodborne. When the Hunter confronts him, it is clear that he has began to transform into a beast.
    Gascoigne can be found after the Hunter finds their way through the Yharnam Aqueducts and crossed
    the bridge with multiple townsfolk blocking the way, as well as a troll who lights a giant ball on
    fire, sending it rolling towards the Hunter and the group of Huntsmen.</string>
    <string name="father_gascoigne_lore">Father Gascoigne is husband to Viola, and father to the young
    girl and her sister that can be found in central Yharnam. When Gascoigne goes out on his hunt,
    Viola ventures out in search of him. When the Hunter interacts with the little girl, she mentions
    that Viola forgot the music box that brings Gascoigne down from his madness and reminds him of
    his family. She also mentions that Viola wears a wonderful red broach. After defeating Gascoigne,
    the Hunter can find Viola and her broach atop the small building in the boss arena. Taking this
    broach back to the little girl will prompt her to become nearly hysterical with grief. Later, her
    ribbon can be found by killing the giant pig in the sewers in the Aqueducts. Return this blood
    soaked ribbon to the little girl\'s older sister to prompt some disturbing dialogue. The older
    sister can later be found at the bottom of the ladder directly beside her house. She either committed
    suicide, or slipped and fell off the ledge.</string>
    <string name="father_gascoigne_fight_strategy">Father Gascoigne has been known to be one of the
    hardest fights in this game, considering how early on he is found. Many of his attacks are able
    to be parried, opening him up to visceral attacks. Combine parried with a quick molotov toss and
    he will go down quite easily. Be wary of his beast phase as he can stunlock the Hunter with his
    leaping attacks, quickly killing them. Parrying his leaps is the best bet for handling this phase,
    as he can still be stunned and visceral attacked after he transforms.</string>
    <string name="father_gascoigne_loot">Father Gascoigne drops some blood echoes and an Oedon Tomb
    key.</string>

    <!-- Gerhman, The First Hunter -->
    <string name="boss_gehrman">Gehrman, The First Hunter</string>
    <string name="boss_gehrman_description">Gehrman is one of the three final bosses of Bloodborne.
    You can find Gehrman in the Hunter\'s Dream throughout the game; however after killing Mergo\'s
    Wet Nurse, Gehrman will have moved to the base of the Great Tree behind the workshop.</string>
    <string name="gehrman_lore">See Old Hunter Gherman NPC page for lore.</string>
    <string name="gehrman_fight_strategy">Gehrman has a very fast, aggressive fight style and is
    considered by many one of the bigger challenges in the game. Becoming incredibly familiar with
    parrying will make this fight less of a burden, as Gehrman is able to be parried throughout the
    fight. Be wary of him when he has his Hunter\'s Pistol out, as it can parry you even if you aren\'t
    attacking. This fight is about patience and learning Gehrman\'s attack patterns. Know which attacks
    do and don\'t do incredible amounts of damage, learn which attacks can be parried and always remain
    patient. </string>
    <string name="gehrman_loot">Gehrman drops an Old Hunter Badge, as well as a large amount of blood
    echoes.</string>

    <!-- Martyr Logarius -->
    <string name="boss_logarius">Martyr Logarius</string>
    <string name="logarius_description">Martyr Logarius can be found on the roof of the Cainhurst castle,
    keeping watch over his prisoner. He is a human but has been twisted from his original form, giving
    him a nightmarish look.</string>
    <string name="logarius_lore">Martyr Logarius was the reason behind the near extinction of the
    Vilebloods. He struck out on a mission to eliminate all the Vilebloods, and succeeded; however,
    Logarius kept Queen Annalise locked up in her keep and shrouded by illusion. He remains warden of
    this prison until the Hunter kills him.</string>
    <string name="logarius_fight_strategy">Martyr Logarius is quite strong against fire, arcane, and
    bolt damage. The key to this fight is to stay patient. Logarius is most vulnerable when he\'s in
    his melee phase.  During this phase Logarius can be parried for large amounts of damage. During
    his magic phase try to work your way around the spells being fired at you for a quick strike or
    two, then move back. Lastly, Logarius will drive his sword into the ground, creating another
    obstacle in the form of endless magic swords that fly towards the Hunter. Breaking the sword planted
    in the gound will end this.</string>
    <string name="logarius_loot">Martyr Logarius gives one insight for finding him, and three more
    for killing him. He also drops a large amount of blood echoes, and the Crown of Illusions. Make
    sure to pick up the crown as it reveals the keep that Queen Annalise resides in.</string>

    <!-- Mergo\'s Wet Nurse-->
    <string name="boss_mergo">Mergo\'s Wet Nurse</string>
    <string name="mergo_description">Mergo\'s Wet Nurse is a tall, almost demonic being with six
    skeletal arms, and a set of black wings. Under it\'s hood, there is nothing. This boss can be
    found at the end of the Nightmare of Mensis, at the top of the tower. As the Hunter gets closer,
    the sound of an infant crying. </string>
    <string name="mergo_lore">Mergo\'s Wet Nurse is a Great One that guards the source of the Nightmare,
    Mergo. Mergo is the daughter of Yharnam, who can be found outside the boss arena. </string>
    <string name="mergo_fight_strategy">This boss is weak to bolt, arcane, and poison attacks. There
    is also a weak spot behind the boss when it\'s attacking. Getting in behind the boss will allow
    the Hunter to attack without taking much damage. The boss will eventually create a purple fog,
    during this phase, in addition to the boss\'s normal attacks, it creates a copy of itself to
    attack the Hunter as well.</string>
    <string name="mergo_loot">Mergo\'s Wet Nurse drops a very large amount of blood echoes, and a One
    Third Umbilical Cord.</string>

    <!-- Micolash, Host of the Nightmare-->
    <string name="boss_micolash">Micolash, Host of the Nightmare</string>
    <string name="micolash_description">Micolash can be found inside the castle in the Nightmare of
    Mensis middle level. He is seen wearing a mensis cage on his head, as well as a tattered Byrgenwerth
    uniform. </string>
    <string name="micolash_lore">Micolash founded the School of Mensis, after the collapse of Byrgenwerth.
    Micolash reported his findings to Lawrence and the Healing Church. </string>
    <string name="micolash_fight_strategy">Micolash strategy here</string>
    <string name="micolash_loot">Micolash loot</string>

    <!-- Moon Presence -->
    <string name="boss_moon_presence">Moon Presence</string>
    <string name="moon_presence_description">Moon Presence is an optional boss at the end of Bloodborne.
    This boss is a Great One and is where the One Third Umbilical Cords come into play. Consuming
    these three items, and killing Gehrman will have a cut scene play of the Moon Presence floating
    down to the Hunter. Once this fight is over, the Hunter will be transformed into a Great One,
    lifting mankind into it\'s next level of being.</string>
    <string name="moon_presence_lore">When the Moon Presence is encountered, it initially wants to
    make the Hunter the next watcher of the Dream, taking Gehrman\'s place. Consuming the three One
    Third Umbilical Cords imbues the Hunter with enough power to resist the Moon Presence, enraging
    it and leading to the \"true\" ending.</string>
    <string name="moon_presence_fight_strategy">Moon Presence is weak to fire and bolt damage, and
    is susceptible to being parried. Watch for the three hit combo that it will often unleash, as this
    is a good time to dodge in behind the boss for some quick damage. This boss is very quick, and
    aggressive, so be patient and watch for it\'s moves that can be parried, and get in behind it
    as much as possible.</string>
    <string name="moon_presence_loot">Moon Presence drops a huge amount of blood echoes, and ends the
    game upon defeat.</string>

    <!-- One Reborn -->
    <string name="boss_one_reborn">One Reborn</string>
    <string name="one_reborn_description">The One Reborn can be found at the bottom of the large sets
    of staircases in Yar\'Ghul after Rom has been defeated. This boss is a massive monstrosity that
    appears to be stitched together out of piles of undead, and beasts alike.</string>
    <string name="one_reborn_lore">The denizens of Yar\'Ghul had been known to kidnap citizens of
    Yharnam, and perform rituals with them. There are even some that speak of hearing screams coming
    from this part of town. As the Hunter delves deeper into Yar\'Ghul, the creatures appear more
    and more to be made of mismatched body parts, and The One Reborn seems to be the masterpiece of
    the experiments.</string>
    <string name="one_reborn_fight_strategy">The One Reborn is known to be a fairly easy fight, as
    long as the Hunter makes sure to eliminate the casters that are up on the balcony. After this,
    head back down to the boss and make sure to avoid the pools of festering ooze that the boss will
    shoot at you. Also keep an eye out for the large AoE attack that the boss will unleash once in a
    while. This attack is very predictable as it has a very long charge up time, if the Hunter fails
    to get out from this AoE attack, there is a good chance of a quick death. To have an additional
    edge for this fight, bring either fire or bolt papers and a weapon with a high rally rate is
    recommended. Stay in near the middle of the boss where the smaller legs with attack with rapid
    fire kicks. If you have brought a weapon with high rally, you can essentially trade damage with
    the boss until it\'s dead.</string>
    <string name="one_reborn_loot">Upon discovery, The One Reborn gives the Hunter one insight, and
    an additional three insight for killing it. When it has been defeated, it rewards the Hunter with
    a hefty amount of blood echoes and three Yellow Backbones.</string>

    <!-- Rom, The Vacuous Spider -->
    <string name="boss_rom">Rom, the Vacuous Spider</string>
    <string name="rom_description">Rom is a Great One boss in Bloodborne, and is the boss that changes
    the game the most when defeated. She can be found at the Moonside Lake after jumping off the
    Byrgenwerth balcony where Master Willem is found.</string>
    <string name="rom_lore">After kiling Rom, the nightmare is revealed and the veil keeping the
    Great Ones apart from the mortal world is torn apart, bring the blood moon upon Yharnam. Rom is
    one of the Infant Great Ones and some believe her to be the child of Ebrietas. At the beginning
    of the fight, Rom is completely non aggressive. Even through her first phase she only ever summons
    spiders to protect her rather than attack the Hunter, suggesting that Rom might not have been one
    of the bad guys.</string>
    <string name="rom_fight_strategy">This boss battle is a bit of a hassle no matter how it is
    tackled. One tried and true method is to bring a Flamesprayer, buffing it with Bone Marrow Ash,
    and spraying Rom until she teleports. Keep a blunt weapon for dealing with the spiders that Rom
    spawns such as a Tonitrus. These guardians are deadly if they attack in quick successions. Lastly,
    avoid Rom\'s AoE attack, it will likely lead to a quick end to the fight. If you don\'t want to
    use the Flamesprayer, a strength weapon paired with Fire Paper is ideal.</string>
    <string name="rom_loot">Rom loot</string>

    <!-- Shadows of Yharnam -->
    <string name="boss_shadows_of_yharnam">Shadows of Yharnam</string>
    <string name="shadows_of_yharnam_description">This trio can be found at the very end of the
    Forbidden Forest, guarding the entrance to Byrgenwerth. They appear in an almost grim reaper fashion,
    dressed in black robes, skeletal figures hidden beneath.</string>
    <string name="shadows_of_yharnam_lore">The Shadows of Yharnam seem to be servants, or worshippers
    of Yharnam, the Pthumerian Queen. They are found guarding Rom in the Forbidden Forest, and Mergo
    in the upper levels of the Nightmare of Mensis. Their guarding of Rom further solidifies the
    belief that Rom was protecting man-kind from making contact with the Great Ones. This would prove
    that Rom and the Shadows of Yharnam aren\'t exactly the bad guys in the game.</string>
    <string name="shadows_of_yharnam_fight_strategy">During this boss fight, try to make sure not to
    get swarmed as this is a fairly common reason for a Hunter to die. Each of these foes has several
    stages that they will transform into if they are either left alive for an extended period of time,
    or one of them is killed. Their first phase is just the trio of them and their core attacks. Once
    they switch to their second phase, allowing their bodies to become hosts for snakes. During this
    phase, these enemies will have extremely enhanced attack range. Their third phase is the point of
    the fight where things become a little tricky as the remaining Shadow will be able to summon enormous
    snakes from the ground beneath you, if these snakes hit, there is a good chance of dieing for the
    Hunter so keep an eye out for the red circles on the ground, or interrupt the Shadow from summoning
    the snakes in the first place. One final bit of information on this fight, the Shadows are fairly
    weak to bolt damage. They are also susceptible to the Shaman Bone Blade, essentially making the
    fight a two on two as long as one Shadow is kept under the Shaman Bone Blade\'s influence.</string>
    <string name="shadows_of_yharnam_loot">Shadows of Yharnam reward the Hunter with two insight for
    their defeat, as well as a good amount of blood echoes and the Blood Rapture rune.</string>

    <!-- Vicar Amelia -->
    <string name="boss_vicar_amelia">Vicar Amelia</string>
    <string name="vicar_amelia_description">Vicar Amelia is the second mandatory boss in Bloodborne
    and can be found in the Grand Cathedral in the Cathedral Ward. The cut scene that plays shows
    this boss in her human form, clutching her Gold Pendant and warning the Hunter to be wary of the
    frailty of men, encouraging the Hunter to seek the Old Blood.</string>
    <string name="vicar_amelia_lore">Vicars in Bloodborne are the heads of the Healing Church. It
    seems that Vicar Amelia was the last Vicar, overseeing the Church as she watched Yharnam crumble
    around her. When the Hunter finds her, she is seen praying to the altar, waiting for her inevitable
    transformation to beast-hood.</string>
    <string name="vicar_amelia_fight_strategy">Vicar Amelia, as with all beast bosses is weak to fire
    damage, so bringing a few Fire Papers is recommended. There is no tried and true safe zone for this
    battle, so the Hunter will have to dodge in and around her attacks to get close enough to strike.
    Attacking Amelia\'s legs will eventually stagger her, opening her up for a visceral attack. The
    second phase of this fight can last an eternity if the Hunter can\'t deal enough damage through
    her healing ability. Bringing some numbing mist is a great way to avoid this as it will stop her
    from healing altogether.</string>
    <string name="vicar_amelia_loot">Discovery of this boss gives the Hunter one insight. Defeating
    her rewards the Hunter with a moderate amount of blood echoes, her Gold Pendant, and three more
    insight.</string>

    <!-- Witch of Hemwick -->
    <string name="boss_witch_of_hemwick">Witch of Hemwick</string>
    <string name="witch_of_hemwick_description">Witch of Hemwick can be found near the end of Hemwick
    Charnel Lane in her abode. This boss is an elite version of the Eye Collectors that can be
    found throughout certain areas of Bloodborne.</string>
    <string name="witch_of_hemwick_lore">The Witch of Hemwick is rumoured to hold special rituals
    deep in the night in her lonely abode. There are whispers of her collecting the eyes of the citizens
    found throughout Yharnam, alive or dead. </string>
    <string name="witch_of_hemwick_fight_strategy">The fight against the Witch of Hemwick is commonly
    referred to as an easy fight. Staying away from the Mad Ones that stalk the Hunter in the boss
    arena, run around until the Witch reveals herself and get as many hits in as you can. Rinse and
    repeat until the second witch appears. The trick to this fight is trying to get both witches to
    die as close to the same time as possible. If one of the witches remains dead for long enough,
    it will be revived with significantly reduced health.</string>
    <string name="witch_of_hemwick_loot">Discovery of the Witch of Hemwick gives the Hunter one insight.
    Killing her gives the Hunter two insight, four bloodshot eyeballs, and a moderate amount of blood
    echoes.</string>

</resources>