<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!-- TODO: This is an inefficient way to handle data, create a storage class, or use a database
         TODO: Make this update happen after launch, get the app out first!-->

    <!-- Enemies string set template:
         Enemy Title:
         Description:
         Associated items/loot:
         Fight Strategy: -->

    <!-- Reference: bloodbornewiki.org, youtube channels, FromSoftware's Bloodborne-->

    <!--String Array used to build Enemies list in enemy_list Activity-->
    <string-array name="enemies_list">
        <item>Beast Patient</item>
        <item>Beast Possessed Soul</item>
        <item>Bloodlicker</item>
        <item>Brain of Mensis</item>
        <item>Brainsucker</item>
        <item>Cainhurst Gargoyle</item>
        <item>Cainhurst Servant</item>
        <item>Carrion Crow</item>
        <item>Celestial Emissary</item>
        <item>Celestial Larvae</item>
        <item>Chime Maiden</item>
        <item>Chapel Giant</item>
        <item>Church Servant</item>
        <item>Cramped Casket</item>
        <item>Crawler</item>
        <item>Executioner</item>
        <item>Eye Collector</item>
        <item>Fluorescent Flower</item>
        <item>Garden of Eyes</item>
        <item>Giant Lost Child</item>
        <item>Giant Hog</item>
        <item>Hemwick Grave Hag</item>
        <item>Hound</item>
        <item>Huntsman</item>
        <item>Giant Rat</item>
        <item>Mad One</item>
        <item>Mergo\'s Attendant</item>
        <item>Mergo\'s Chief Attendant</item>
        <item>Nightmare Apostle</item>
        <item>Hateful Maggot</item>
        <item>Rotted Corpse</item>
        <item>Scourge Beast</item>
        <item>Silver Beast</item>
        <item>Silver Lady</item>
        <item>Slime Scholar</item>
        <item>Shadow of Yharnam</item>
        <item>Skeletal Puppet</item>
        <item>Snatcher</item>
        <item>Troll</item>
        <item>Vermin Host</item>
        <item>Wheelchair Huntsman</item>
        <item>Winter Lantern</item>
    </string-array>

     <!--Beast Patient-->
    <string name="ememy_beast_patient">Beast Patient</string>
    <string name="beast_patient_description">Beast Patients can be found throughout Yharnam and beyond.
    They are the outcome of the purge of Old Yharnam and are seen wearing bandages to cover their
    burn wounds.</string>
    <string name="beast_patient_fight_strategy">Beast Patients are weak against fire. They are also
    fairly quick so dodging in behind them and attacking is recommended. Another tactic to fighting
    these foes is to memorize their attack range and bait them into attacking while remaining just
    outside of the beast\'s range. One the beast is finished it\'s attack, go in for the kill.</string>
    <string name="beast_patient_items_loot">Beast Patient drops blood vials and a variety of
    gemstones</string>

    <!-- Beast Possessed Soul-->
    <string name="ememy_beast_possessed_soul">Beast Possessed Soul</string>
    <string name="beast_possessed_soul_description">This creature is found at the bottom of the Healing
    Church Workshop. It\'s use of magical attacks mixed with vicious physical attacks makes it a foe
    to be reckoned with.</string>
    <string name="beast_possessed_soul_fight_strategy">The Beast Possessed Soul is a dangerous enemy
    for the unsuspecting Hunter. It generally moves quite slowly, and can be parried for a nice visceral
    attack.</string>
    <string name="beast_possessed_soul_items_loot">The Beast Possessed Soul drops a Beast rune.</string>

    <!-- Bloodlicker -->
    <string name="ememy_bloodlicker">Bloodlicker</string>
    <string name="bloodlicker_description">Bloodlickers can be found in the first outdoors area in the
    Cainhurst castle. It is very hard to miss these enemies with their deformed, hunched over bodies,
    and the giant sack of blood hanging like a giant red belly. These are one of the more difficult
    enemies to take down. </string>
    <string name="bloodlicker_fight_strategy">Bloodlickers are incredibly fast, and hit incredibly hard.
    If you plan on taking it down, try to listen for it\'s telltale hiss. When it makes this noise,
    be ready to dodge behind it as these creatures always attack after making a hiss. Also be aware
    of their donkey kick if attacking from behind these creatures. Another thing to keep in mind is
    that Bloodlickers are not susceptible to visceral attacks.</string>
    <string name="bloodlicker_items_loot">Bloodlickers drop bloodtinge gemstones of varying levels.</string>

    <!-- Brain of Mensis -->
    <string name="ememy_brain_of_mensis">Brain of Mesis</string>
    <string name="brain_of_mensis_description">This foe can be found in a pit within the Nightmare
    of Mensis. After killing Micolash and finding the lever to drop this enemy into the black pit,
    go to the elevators on the Middle Tier of the Nightmare. About halfway down there is a window to
    jump through. Navigate this path until you come across a bridge. Pull the lever at the end of the
    bridge to have the Brain of Mensis dropped from it\'s chains. After that, drop down the hole near
    the lever. Run out of the building and follow this path until you find a building with Mergo\'s
    Attendants. Navigate to the lower level and take the elevator that seems to descend into nothing
    but darkness. This is where the Brain of Mensis will be residing.</string>
    <string name="brain_of_mensis_fight_strategy">The Brain of Mesis is not aggressive if attacked in
    the black pit.</string>
    <string name="brain_of_mensis_items_loot">This enemy will give the Hunter a tier three Moon Rune
    if the \"Make Contact\" gesture is held until the Hunter rotates their arms. Upon killing this
    creature, a Living string is dropped.</string>

    <!-- Brainsucker -->
    <string name="ememy_brainsucker">Brainsucker</string>
    <string name="brainsucker_description">Brainsucker can be found throughout the entire game. Some
    are seen wearing hoods, and others not. This appears to be for appearance\'s sake as it makes no
    difference to the tactics and abilities this enemy can use.</string>
    <string name="brainsucker_fight_strategy">Brainsuckers have multiple spells that they will use to
    stun the Hunter, opening them up to their favourite ability, sucking the insight straight from your
    brain. Avoid their stun attacks and try to have a weapon with high thrust damage as these foes are
    weak to thrust.</string>
    <string name="brainsucker_items_loot">Brainsuckers drop Quicksilver Bulltes and Shaman Bone Blades.</string>

    <!-- Cainhurst Servant -->
    <string name="ememy_cainhurst_servant">Cainhurst Servant</string>
    <string name="cainhurst_servant_description">Cainhurst Servants can  be found scrubbing the interior
    of Cainhurst Castle. They serve Queen Annalise as both castle servants and knights.</string>
    <string name="cainhurst_servant_fight_strategy">Cainhurst Servants are not normally aggressive
    and will focus on maintaining the castle. Once provoked, they will become quite hostile with
    deceitfully long ranged attacks. The key to fighting these foes is to either kill them before they
    become aggressive, or wait at a distance until they begin one of their combos and dodge in behind
    them, allowing for a large amount of damage to be dealt. Be wary of the librarian servants as they
    are qeuipped with an ability to shoot darts at you, enraging the Phantom Ladies.</string>
    <string name="cainhurst_servant_items_loot">Cainhurst Servants drop Quicksilver Bullets and
    Numbing Mists.</string>

    <!-- Carrion Crow -->
    <string name="ememy_carrion_crow">Carrion Crow</string>
    <string name="carrion_crow_description">Carrion Crows can be found all through Bloodborne, both
    in the city of Yharnam, and the Nightmare of Mensis. They appear to have crippled legs and will
    usually just watch the Hunter as long as a bit of distance is kept from them.</string>
    <string name="carrion_crow_fight_strategy">These foes have a particularly deceitful ability to
    ignore the attacks of the Hunter, getting in hit combos which can be a drain on blood vials.
    Outside of this mechanic, Carrion Crows aren\'t anything to fret about.</string>
    <string name="carrion_crow_items_loot">Carrion Crows generally drop pebbles, but have also been
    known to drop antidotes, and beast blood pellets.</string>

    <!-- Celestial Larvae -->
    <string name="ememy_celestial_larvae">Celestial Larvae</string>
    <string name="celestial_larvae_description">Celestial Larvae can be found in the Upper Cathedral
    Ward. These creatures are believed to be the children that once lived in the Orphanage, or perhaps
    cross bred offspring of the Great One, Ebrietas who dwells underneath the Orphanage.</string>
    <string name="celestial_larvae_fight_strategy">Bring sedatives. Having these will eliminate any
    threat that these creatures possess as they rely on causing frenzy on the Hunter to inflict major
    damage.</string>
    <string name="celestial_larvae_items_loot">Celestial Larvae drop Madman\'s Knowledge occasionally</string>

    <!-- Chime Maiden -->
    <string name="ememy_chime_maiden">Chime Maiden</string>
    <string name="chime_maiden_description">Chime Maiden can be found throughout Bloodborne in certain
    areas and are capable of summoning invaders into the Hunter\'s own nightmare. Additionally, these
    enemies will be spawned when the Hunter uses a beckoning bell. There are two variants of this
    enemy. The first variant revives enemies that you have killed. The second variant will summon
    invaders into your nightmare.</string>
    <!-- TODO: Rewrite last sentence to explain the stun effect better -->
    <string name="chime_maiden_fight_strategy">The greatest challenge of killing Chime Maidens is
    finding them. These sneaky foes will generally be tucked away in some hard to find, or highly
    guarded area. Once found, they will die quite easily, and stun any of it\'s raised allies.</string>
    <string name="chime_maiden_items_loot">Chime Maidens drop quicksilver bullets.</string>

    <!-- Chapel Giant -->
    <string name="ememy_chapel_giant">Chapel Giant</string>
    <string name="chapel_giant_description">Chapel Giants are incredibly large enemies that can be found
    lumbering throughout the cathedral ward and the Nightmare Frontier. There are also variants
    underneath Iosefka\'s clinic called Undead Giants.</string>
    <string name="chapel_giant_fight_strategy">Chapel Giants are susceptible to being parried. Nailing
    the timing on parries to get in a visceral attack is one of the most effective ways to kill these
    enemies. The safer way to eliminate these foes is to dodge in behind the giant, and get as many
    attacks in as possible before it turns. Dodging with the Giant\'s turn to remain behind it is also
    extremely effective.</string>
    <string name="chapel_giant_items_loot">Chapel Giants drop Blood Stone Shards, Blood Vials, and
    less often, Blue Elixirs.</string>

    <!-- Church Servant -->
    <string name="ememy_church_servant">Church Servant</string>
    <string name="church_servant_description">Church Servants can be found in a variety of locales in
    Yharnam and beyond. The largest cluster of these enemies is in  the Cathedral Ward. These enemies
    have many variations and all are deadly if not properly evaded.</string>
    <string name="church_servant_fight_strategy">Church Servants hit quite hard when they\'re first
    encountered. Luckily, they move quite slowly, so it\'s very easy to dodge in behind them and get
    a couple attacks in before they swing around with a vicious attack. These enemies are also able
    to be parried, enabling the Hunter to finish them in a matter of seconds.</string>
    <string name="church_servant_items_loot">Church Servants drop Blood Vials, Quicksilver Bullets, and
    Blue Elixirs.</string>

    <!-- Cramped Casket -->
    <string name="ememy_cramped_casket">Cramped Casket</string>
    <!-- The caskets in earlier areas of the game have been chained shut... is this to keep these guys
     contained inside of the casket? -->
    <string name="cramped_casket_description">Cramped Casket\'s are believed to be the outcome of some
    sort of dark magic used on a casket overstuffed with corpses. These foes can be found inside
    Yar\'Ghul, the Unseen Village after Rom has been defeated.</string>
    <string name="cramped_casket_fight_strategy">Cramped Caskets have a lot of health, and deal some
    serious damage. If they find themselves out of range of the Hunter, it will either make use of it\'s
    plethora of arms to close in quickly for an attack, or shoot an impaled corpse at the Hunter
    Staying out of it\'s frontal area of attack is the wisest thing to do with these enemies as they
    area capable of ending a fight before you can say \"Yharnam\". Get in behind, and stay there by
    strafing/dodging when the Cramped Casket begins to turn, or do it\'s wide sweeping attack.</string>
    <string name="cramped_casket_items_loot">Cramped Caskets will generally drop blood gems.</string>

    <!-- Crawler(has variants) -->
    <string name="ememy_crawler">Crawler</string>
    <string name="crawler_description">Crawlers can be found in clusters in the nightmare frontier in
    the large pits of acid throughout. They don\'t vary all that much aside from their size. </string>
    <string name="crawler_fight_strategy">These foes aren\'t too daunting to face one on one, so
    when you come across a cluster of Crawlers, lure one out at a time. Be cautious of their ranged
    spit attack.</string>
    <string name="crawler_items_loot">Crawlers drop Thick Coldblood</string>

    <!-- Executioner -->
    <string name="ememy_executioner">Executioner</string>
    <string name="executioner_description">Executioners are the enemies found throughout Yharnam and
    beyond carrying extremely large axes. These enemies can cause a large amount of frustration early
    in the game due to their severely high damage output.</string>
    <string name="executioner_fight_strategy">Executioners are vulnerable to being parried. Wait for
    them to charge up their jumping lunge attack and right when they\'re about to lunge, shoot them.
    Get in the visceral attack and get ready to keep fighting as these enemies have above average HP.
    If trying to dodge in behind this enemy, be aware that it will utilize multiple attacks that can
    still damage you.</string>
    <string name="executioner_items_loot">Executioner can drop Tempering Blood Gemstones, Blood Vials,
    and Pungent Blood Cocktails.</string>

    <!-- Eye Collector -->
    <string name="ememy_eye_collector">Eye Collector</string>
    <string name="eye_collector_description">Eye Collectors can be found in the Hypogean Gaol and are
    practically lesser versions of the Witch of Hemwick boss. They have no magical attacks, but if they
    grab you, they will gouge your eyes out in the same fashion the Witch of Hemwick does. </string>
    <string name="eye_collector_fight_strategy">Eye Collectors are strong to Bolt damage, and weak to
    nearly everything else. If you ever do get grabbed by one of these enemies, mash L1,L2,R1, and R2
    to escape a little bit quicker than normal.</string>
    <string name="eye_collector_items_loot">Eye Collectors drop Pebbles and Bloodshot Eyeballs.</string>

    <!-- Fluorescent Flower -->
    <string name="ememy_fluorescent_flower">Fluorescent Flower</string>
    <!-- TODO: Find a better way to describe this creature. -->
    <string name="fluorescent_flower_description">Fluorescent Flowers can be found in Byrgenwerth.
    These giant creatures resemble a cross between a millipede and a ultra brightly coloured flower
    bouquet.</string>
    <string name="fluorescent_flower_fight_strategy">Fluorescent Flowers can be quite dangerous due
    to their size and variety of attacks. Be sure to avoid their long ranged fire ball attacks.
    Find your way to either it\'s blind spot close to the center of it\'s body and go nuts. Be wary
    of it\'s sweeping side swipe attack when in close, being careful not to dodge backwards as the
    range of this attack is difficult to memorize for a while.</string>
    <string name="fluorescent_flower_items_loot">Fluorescent Flowers drop Arcane Haze.</string>

    <!-- Garden of Eyes -->
    <string name="ememy_garden_of_eyes">Garden of Eyes</string>
    <string name="garden_of_eyes_description">Garden of Eyes can be found in Byrgenwerth. These
    creatures appear to be a cross between a man who line it\'s brains with eyes, as Willem suggested,
    and a bat or insectoid of some sort.</string>
    <string name="garden_of_eyes_fight_strategy">Garden of Eyes have one deadly attack, and that is
    their leaping grab attack. If this attack lands, it will begin building frenzy and can kill the
    Hunter if they\'re unprepared. Caution is advised when travelling through Byrgenwerth until all
    locations of these enemies are memorized. Remember to mash L1,L2,R1, and R2 to escape grab attacks
    more quickly.</string>
    <string name="garden_of_eyes_items_loot">Garden of Eyes drop Quicksilver Bullets and Sedatives.</string>

    <!-- Giant Lost Child -->
    <string name="ememy_giant_lost_child">Giant Lost Child</string>
    <string name="giant_lost_child_description">Giant Lost Children can be found in the Nightmare
    Frontier. These enemies are a variant of the Chapel Giants, but they\'ve been warped in the
    Nightmare to the point of having a separate entry.</string>
    <string name="giant_lost_child_fight_strategy">Giant Lost Children are a huge nuisance in the
    Nightmare Frontier as they have the ability to hurl boulders over incredible distances. These
    boulders not only do extraordinary damage if they hit the Hunter, they also do huge amounts of
    damage if the Hunter is even close to the explosion the boulder causes. This is the largest threat
    these foes present and are a matter of staying behind it while close up. Be wary of other Giant
    Lost Children while closing in on one, their boulders will not wait while you kill the current
    target Giant.</string>
    <string name="giant_lost_child_items_loot">Giant Lost Children drop Blood Stone Shards, or Twin
    Blood Stone Shards, depending on what section of the Nightmare the Hunter is in. They also drop
    Lead Elixirs.</string>

    <!-- Hemwick Grave Hag -->
    <string name="ememy_grave_hag">Hemwick Grave Hag</string>
    <string name="grave_hag_description">Hemwick Grave Hags are found throughout Hemwick Charnel Lane.
    These enemies worship the Witch of Hemwick, and are found circled around a statue dedicated to
    the Witch. They give away their locations with quiet mumblings, crying, laughing, or screaming.
    They can always be heard, manic and deadly.</string>
    <string name="grave_hag_fight_strategy">Hemwick Grave Hags lack any sort of aggressive speed, but
    they will overpower the Hunter if taken too lightly. They have low HP, so wait for an opening, and
    attack until they\'re dead. Be cautious of being swarmed by these enemies as this will result in
    a quick death. If swarmed, keep some distance and use a long range weapon with a sweeping style
    attack. </string>
    <string name="grave_hag_items_loot">Hemwick Grave Hags are known to drop Blood Vials, Quicksilver
    Bullets, Blood Gems and Molotov Cocktails.</string>

    <!-- Hound -->
    <string name="ememy_hound">Hound</string>
    <string name="hound_description">Hound</string>
    <string name="hound_fight_strategy">Hound</string>
    <string name="hound_items_loot">Hound</string>

    <!-- Huntsman -->
    <string name="ememy_huntsman">Huntsman</string>
    <string name="huntsman_description">Huntsman</string>
    <string name="huntsman_fight_strategy">Huntsman</string>
    <string name="huntsman_items_loot">Huntsman</string>

    <!-- Troll (Brick Troll, Log Troll, ...trolls, slow fuckers-->
    <string name="ememy_troll">Troll</string>
    <string name="troll_description">Troll</string>
    <string name="troll_fight_strategy">Troll</string>
    <string name="troll_items_loot">Troll</string>

    <!-- Snatcher(move to appropriate spot on list -->
    <string name="ememy_snatcher">Snatcher</string>
    <string name="snatcher_description">Snatcher</string>
    <string name="snatcher_fight_strategy">Snatcher</string>
    <string name="snatcher_items_loot">Snatcher</string>

    <!-- Giant Pig -->
    <string name="ememy_giant_pig">Giant Pig</string>
    <string name="giant_pig_description">Giant Pig</string>
    <string name="giant_pig_fight_strategy">Giant Pig</string>
    <string name="giant_pig_items_loot">Giant Pig</string>

    <!-- Giant Rat -->
    <string name="ememy_giant_rat">Giant Rat</string>
    <string name="giant_rat_description">Giant Rat</string>
    <string name="giant_rat_fight_strategy">Giant Rat</string>
    <string name="giant_rat_items_loot">Giant Rat</string>

    <!-- Viper Pits -->
    <string name="ememy_viper_pit">Viper Pits</string>
    <string name="viper_pit_description">Viper Pits</string>
    <string name="viper_pit_fight_strategy">Viper Pits</string>
    <string name="viper_pit_items_loot">Viper Pits</string>

    <!-- Cainhurst Gargoyle(Move up in this list for alphabetical order) -->
    <string name="ememy_cainhurst_gargoyle">Cainhirst Gargoyle</string>
    <string name="cainhurst_gargoyle_description">Cainhirst Gargoyle</string>
    <string name="cainhurst_gargoyle_fight_strategy">Cainhirst Gargoyle</string>
    <string name="cainhurst_gargoyle_items_loot">Cainhirst Gargoyle</string>

    <!-- Mad One -->
    <string name="ememy_mad_one">Mad One</string>
    <string name="mad_one_description">Mad One</string>
    <string name="mad_one_fight_strategy">Mad One</string>
    <string name="mad_one_items_loot">Mad One</string>

    <!-- Mergo\'s Attendant -->
    <string name="ememy_mergos_attendant">Mergo\'s Attendant</string>
    <string name="mergos_attendant_description">Mergo\'s Attendant</string>
    <string name="mergos_attendant_fight_strategy">Mergo\'s Attendant</string>
    <string name="mergos_attendant_items_loot">Mergo\'s Attendant</string>

    <!-- Mergo\'s Chief Attendant -->
    <string name="ememy_mergos_chief_attendant">Mergo\'s Chief Attendant</string>
    <string name="mergos_chief_attendant_description">Mergo\'s Chief Attendant</string>
    <string name="mergos_chief_attendant_fight_strategy">Mergo\'s Chief Attendant</string>
    <string name="mergos_chief_attendant_items_loot">Mergo\'s Chief Attendant</string>

    <!-- Nightmare Apostle (has variants)-->
    <string name="ememy_nightmare_apostle">Nightmare Apostle</string>
    <string name="nightmare_apostle_description">Nightmare Apostle</string>
    <string name="nightmare_apostle_fight_strategy">Nightmare Apostle</string>
    <string name="nightmare_apostle_items_loot">Nightmare Apostle</string>

    <!-- Hateful Maggot-->
    <string name="ememy_hateful_maggot">Hateful Maggot</string>
    <string name="hateful_maggot_description">Hateful Maggot</string>
    <string name="hateful_maggot_fight_strategy">Hateful Maggot</string>
    <string name="hateful_maggot_items_loot">Hateful Maggot</string>

    <!-- Rotted Corpse -->
    <string name="ememy_rotted_corpse">Rotted Corpse</string>
    <string name="rotted_corpse_description">Rotted Corpse</string>
    <string name="rotted_corpse_fight_strategy">Rotted Corpse</string>
    <string name="rotted_corpse_items_loot">Rotted Corpse</string>

    <!-- Slime Scholars -->
    <string name="ememy_slime_scholar">Slime Scholars</string>
    <string name="slime_scholar_description">Slime Scholars</string>
    <string name="slime_scholar_fight_strategy">Slime Scholars</string>
    <string name="slime_scholar_items_loot">Slime Scholars</string>

    <!-- Scourge Beast -->
    <string name="ememy_scourge_beast">Scourge Beast</string>
    <string name="scourge_beast_description">Scourge Beast</string>
    <string name="scourge_beast_fight_strategy">Scourge Beast</string>
    <string name="scourge_beast_items_loot">Scourge Beast</string>

    <!-- Shadow of Yharnam -->
    <string name="ememy_shadow_of_yharnam">Shadow of Yharnam</string>
    <string name="shadow_of_yharnam_description">Shadow of Yharnam</string>
    <string name="shadow_of_yharnam_fight_strategy">Shadow of Yharnam</string>
    <string name="shadow_of_yharnam_items_loot">Shadow of Yharnam</string>

    <!-- Silver Lady -->
    <string name="ememy_silver_lady">Silver Lady</string>
    <string name="silver_lady_description">Silver Lady</string>
    <string name="silver_lady_fight_strategy">Silver Lady</string>
    <string name="silver_lady_items_loot">Silver Lady</string>x

    <!-- Skeletal Puppet -->
    <string name="ememy_skeletal_puppet">Skeletal Puppet</string>
    <string name="skeletal_puppet_description">Skeletal Puppet</string>
    <string name="skeletal_puppet_fight_strategy">Skeletal Puppet</string>
    <string name="skeletal_puppet_items_loot">Skeletal Puppet</string>

    <!-- Celestial Emissary (has variants, move to appropriate spot in list for alphabetical reasons -->
    <string name="ememy_celestial_emissary">Celestial Emissary</string>
    <string name="enemy_celestial_emissary_description">Celestial Emissary</string>
    <string name="enemy_celestial_emissary_fight_strategy">Celestial Emissary</string>
    <string name="enemy_celestial_emissary_items_loot">Celestial Emissary</string>

    <!-- Vermin Host -->
    <string name="ememy_vermin_host">Vermin Host</string>
    <string name="vermin_host_description">Vermin Host</string>
    <string name="vermin_host_fight_strategy">Vermin Host</string>
    <string name="vermin_host_items_loot">Vermin Host</string>

    <!-- Wheelchair Huntsman -->
    <string name="ememy_wheelchair_huntsman">Wheelchair Huntsman</string>
    <string name="wheelchair_huntsman_description">Wheelchair Huntsman</string>
    <string name="wheelchair_huntsman_fight_strategy">Wheelchair Huntsman</string>
    <string name="wheelchair_huntsman_items_loot">Wheelchair Huntsman</string>

    <!-- Winter Lantern -->
    <string name="ememy_winter_lantern">Winter Lantern</string>
    <string name="winter_lantern_description">Winter Lantern</string>
    <string name="winter_lantern_fight_strategy">Winter Lantern</string>
    <string name="winter_lantern_items_loot">Winter Lantern</string>

</resources>