<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!-- Template for NPC string set, comment before each one for separation-->
    <!-- NPC name:-->
    <!-- NPC description, where its found(if in game)-->
    <!-- Associated items-->
    <!-- Quest line guide(if they have one), lore-->

    <!-- String Array of NPC names for NPC list -->
    <string-array name="npc_names">
        <item>Adella the Nun</item>
        <item>Afflicted Beggar</item>
        <item>Alfred, Hunter of VileBloods</item>
        <item>Annalise, Queen of the VileBloods</item>
        <item>Arianna, Lady of the Night</item>
        <item>Blood Minister</item>
        <item>Chapel Dweller</item>
        <item>Doll</item>
        <item>Eileen the Crow</item>
        <item>Gilbert</item>
        <item>Iosefka</item>
        <item>Lonely Old Woman</item>
        <item>Narrow Minded Man</item>
        <item>Old Hunter Gehrman</item>
        <item>Patches the Spider</item>
        <item>Provost Willem</item>
        <item>Retired Hunter Djura</item>
        <item>Valtr</item>
        <item>Young Girl and Older Sister</item>
    </string-array>


    <!-- THESE STRING SETS WILL BE USED WITHIN THE ARTICLES THEMSELVES, THE ARRAY-LIST WILL BE
         USED FOR, YOU GUESSED IT, THE LIST -->

    <!-- Adella the Nun string set-->
    <string name="npc_adella">Adella the Nun</string>
    <string name="adella_description">Adella is a nun of the Healing Church, and can be found in Yahar-Gul
    crying and praying for help. She is one of the few NPC\'s that can be sent to Oedon Chapel.</string>
    <string name="adella_items">Adella provides the Hunter with the Blood of Adella, an item that gives
    the Hunter health immediately, as well as slowly restoring the Hunter\'s health over time.</string>
    <string name="adella_quest_guide">Adella\'s quest is relatively short, but is slightly confusing as
    she won\'t talk to the Hunter unless they are wearing a torso piece of the Healing Church.</string>

    <!-- Afflicted Beggar string set-->
    <string name="npc_afflicted_beggar">Afflicted Beggar</string>
    <string name="afflicted_beggar_description">The Afflicted Beggar can be found on the roof of one
    of the windmills in the forbidden forest. He appears to have elongated arms, hinting at his impending
    transformation. This becomes apparent when the Hunter attacks him. The beggar will transform into
    a beast and give the Hunter a fight to remember.</string>
    <string name="afflicted_beggar_items">Drops a Beast rune if killed.</string>
    <string name="afflicted_beggar_quest_guide">This NPC is another one of the people that can be sent
    to a safe zone; however he does not act quite so innocent as he may seem. If he is sent to the Oedon
    Chapel, he will slowly kill the rest of the NPC\'s. It is recommended to kill this NPC when he is
    found for the large amount of blood echoes he drops in beast form.</string>

    <!-- Alfred, Hunter of Vilebloods string set-->
    <string name="npc_alfred">Alfred, Hunter of Vilebloods</string>
    <string name="alfred_description">Alfred can be found in the Cathedral Ward outside the tomb the
    leads to Old Yharnam. Alfred is a very friendly NPC and will talk at length about the various details
    of Yharnam and it\'s citizens. Later in the game he moves to the a different spot in the Cathedral
    Ward, overlooking the entrance to the Forbidden Forest.</string>
    <string name="alfred_items">Speaking with Alfred will provide the player with several Fire Papers,
    and killing him gives the Hunter the Wheel Hunter Badge, opening up items to buy from the messengers.</string>
    <string name="alfred_quest_guide">Speak with Alfred at the Cathedral Ward, and tell him you want to help
    him hunt the Bilebloods. After this progress through the game until Martyr Logarius is killed.
    Equip the Crown of Illusions, revealing the Vileblood Queen\'s chamber/prison. To the right of her
    is a table with an unopened summons that the Hunter can give to Alfred, granting him access to
    Cainhurst Castle. Return to the Cainhurt Castle Queen\'s chamber to find Alfred standing over Queen
    Annalise\'s remains. The Hunter can loot Queenly Flesh from the throne, and receives the Roar gesture
    from Alfred. The final part of this quest line inolves finding Alfred at his original spot, dead.
    The Hunter can loot the Radiance rune from his body. </string>

    <!-- Annalise, Queen of the Vilebloods string set-->
    <string name="npc_annalise">Annalise, Queen of the Vilebloods</string>
    <string name="annalise_description">Annalise is the last remaining member of the Vilebloods, a group
    of vampire like creatures born from the Forbidden Blood.The rest of the Vilebloods were wiped
    out by Martyr Logarius. Annalise is kept locked up in her keep/prison by Logarius.</string>
    <string name="annalise_items">Joining the Vilebloood\'s covenant rewards the player with the
    Cainhurst Badge, granting access to the Cainhurst Armour set and the Chikage weapon. Killing her
    rewards the player with some blood echoes and Queenly Flesh.</string>
    <string name="annalise_quest_guide">Annalise\'s quest involves killing Martyr Logarius and looting
    the Crown of Illusions to discover Annalise\'s keep. After this there are several different quest
    lines associated with her; however her own quest line is joining her covenant and finding Blood
    Dregs to give her. </string>

    <!-- Arianna, Lady of the Night string set-->
    <string name="npc_arianna">Arianna, Lady of the Night</string>
    <string name="arianna_description">Arianna is a prostitute that can be found in the Cathedral
    Ward. After defeating approx. three bosses(including the cleric beast, which is optional)
    she can be sent to the Oedon Chapel to be kept safe(recommended), or sent to Iosefka\'s clinic
    for experimentation.</string>
    <string name="arianna_items">Arianna gives the Hunter the Curtsy gesture, and the Blood of Arianna
     blood vial. Later in the game she will provide means to obtain a One Third Umbilical Cord.</string>
    <string name="arianna_quest_guide">Completing Arianna\'s quest line requires the Hunter to send
    her to the Oedon Chapel for safety and keeping her alive long enough for her to give birth to
    an infant Great One. To do this the Hunter must not accept her blood, and avoid sending the
    Inflicted Beggar to Oedon Chapel as he will slowly kill all the other NPC\'s there. After killing
    Micolash, Arianna will have given birth to an infant Great One and moved to the room between the Oedon
    Chapel and the Tomb of Oedon. Kill the child(Arianna will die as well) to obtain a One Third
    Umbilical Cord.</string>

    <!-- Blood Minister string set-->
    <string name="npc_blood_minister">Blood Minister</string>
    <string name="blood_minister_description">The Blood Minister is the first NPC that the Hunter
    will come across, and is only seen during the opening cut scene. He infuses the player with Yharnam
    blood, transforming the player into the Hunter.</string>
    <string name="blood_minister_items">The Blood Minister gives the Hunter a contract to sign, which
    is when the player gets to choose their heritage, looks and name. Although this is not a tangible
    item throughout the game, it is quite important.</string>
    <string name="blood_minister_quest_guide"></string>

    <!-- Chapel Samaritan string set-->
    <string name="npc_chapel_dweller">Chapel Dweller</string>
    <string name="chapel_dweller_description">The Chapel Dweller is the NPC that the Hunter first
    comes across in the Oedon chapel. It is clear from the first time speaking with him that he\'s
    blind as he states that the incense masked the Hunter\'s scent as they approach. This NPC remains
    friendly throughout the entire game so it is not recommended the player kill him as he only drops
    a Formless Oedon rune, and a very depressing dialogue.</string>
    <string name="chapel_dweller_items">Drops a Formless Oedon rune when killed. Also rewards the
    Hunter with the Triumph gesture when the elderly lady is sent to the Chapel.</string>
    <string name="chapel_dweller_quest_guide">The Chapel Dweller provides the Hunter with the option
    to send sane survivors the Oedon Chapel the wait the hunt out in safety. Sending all the
    optional NPC\'s to the Chapel will lead to unsavory results as the Chapel Dweller gets very upset
    when any of the survivors die. To avoid this, don\'t send the Afflicted Beggar to the Oedon Chapel,
    and avoid accepting the Blood of Arianna.</string>

    <!--Doll-->
    <string name="npc_doll">Doll</string>
    <string name="doll_description">The Doll can be found in the Hunter\'s Dream and is used to channel
    blood echoes gained on the hunt. She occasionally falls asleep if the Hunter goes out on a long
    hunt. This NPC is only available after the Hunter has gained one insight. This can be done by
    consuming a madman\'s knowledge, killing the Cleric Beast, or killing Father Gascoigne.</string>
    <string name="doll_items">Giving the Doll the Small Hair Ornament, the Doll will reward the
    Hunter with a Tear Stone, which can be turned into a droplet that fits any gem slot.</string>
    <string name="doll_quest_guide">At the end of the game, if the Hunter becomes an Infant Great One,
    the Doll will pick the Hunter up and cradle their new form, comforting them.</string>

    <!-- Eileen the Crow string set-->
    <string name="npc_eileen">Eileen the Crow</string>
    <string name="eileen_description">Eileen description here</string>
    <string name="eileen_items">Items associated with Eileen here</string>
    <string name="eileen_quest_guide">Eileen quest guide here</string>

    <!-- Gilbert string set-->
    <string name="npc_gilbert">Gilbert</string>
    <string name="gilbert_description">Gilbert is one of the first NPC\'s that the player comes across
    and can be found very close to the Central Yharnam lantern. Speaking with him provides the player
    with information regarding Yharnam and it\'s citizens. He also acknowledges the fact that he is in
    a bad condition and unable to even walk at the beginning of the game.</string>
    <string name="gilbert_items">Once the Hunter has defeated Father Gascoigne, Gilbert will provide
    the Hunter with a Flamesprayer, and effective weapon against beasts. When Gilbert is killed he
    drops some blood echoes and a Beast rune.</string>
    <string name="gilbert_quest_guide">Progressing far enough through the game and returning to Central
    Yharnam, the Hunter will find Gilbert broken out of his window, and fully transformed into a beast.</string>

    <!-- Iosefka string set-->
    <string name="npc_iosefka">Iosefka</string>
    <string name="iosefka_description">Iosefka is an interesting character as she is actually two
    characters. The true Iosefka can be spoken with at the beginning of the game and is kind, and gentle.
    The true Iosefka provides the Hunter with Iosefka\'s Blood Vial when the Hunter has run out. The
    impostor is much more maniacal and agressive in her interactions.</string>
    <string name="iosefka_items">The true Iosefka will give the Hunter Iosefka\'s Blood Vial when
    spoken with as long as the Hunter doesn\'t already have one. The imposter will reward the Hunter
    with an assortment of Numbing Mists, Lead Elixirs, and Insight for sending NPC\'s to her clinic
    for experimentation. Killing her while she is still hostile in her clinic will reward the Hunter
    with an Oedon Writhe rune. Killing her when she is pregnant and weak on the table in her clinic
    will reward the player with a One Third Umbilical Cord(recommended).</string>
    <string name="iosefka_quest_guide">Iosekfa has three stages that she can be interacted with. the
    first is at the beginning of the game when the true Iosefka is running her clinic. After dicovering
    the Cathderal Ward, the impostor kidnaps the true Iosefka and begins her experiments on NPC\'s that
    the Hunter sends her. This is the stage that she can be found inside of her clinic still hostile.
    After the Blood Moon phase of the game begins, the impostor enters her third stage and is pregnant
    with an Infant Great One. Killing her during this stage is recommended as it rewards the Hunter
    with a One Third Umbilical Cord.</string>

    <!-- Lonely Old Woman string set-->
    <string name="npc_old_woman">Lonely Old Woman</string>
    <string name="old_woman_description">The Lonely Old Woman is one of the NPC\'s that can be sent
    to the Oedon Chapel for safety. She can be found just past the area with the group of hounds in
    Central Yharnam. At first she seems to be quite bitter and blames the Hunter for the circumstances
    that Yharnam is in.</string>
    <string name="old_woman_items">The Lonely Old Woman provides the Hunter with Sedatives for their
    hunt after progressing through the game far enough. </string>
    <string name="old_woman_quest_guide">Starting off bitter and eager to have the Hunter leave her be;
    however the more bosses that the Hunter brings down, the more her mood changes. As the moon
    transitions to the grey phase, she descends to madness and can only respond to the Hunter with tears.
    During the blood moon phase, it is believed that madness has fully taken her as she makes a flip
    switch in her mood and is incredibly kind to the Hunter, offering Sedatives, eventually even
    going out into Yharnam to look for more if she runs out. Abusing this will eventually lead to her
    death. Her body can be found just outside of the Oedon Chapel, or what remains of her body.</string>


    <!-- Narrow Minded Man string set-->
    <string name="npc_narrow_minded_man">Narrow Minded Man</string>
    <string name="narrow_minded_man_description">The Narrow Minded Man can be found across the alley
    from where Arianna was found. He is another NPC that can be sent to the Oedon Chapel or to Iosefka\'s
    Clinic.</string>
    <string name="narrow_minded_man_items"></string>
    <string name="narrow_minded_man_quest_guide">This NPC will only listen to the Hunter when Arianna
    has found her way to either the Oedon Chapel or Iosefka\'s Clinic. He travels to the opposite
    destination that the Hunter tells him about.</string>

    <!-- Old Hunter Gehrman string set-->
    <string name="npc_gehrman">Old Hunter Gehrman</string>
    <string name="gehrman_description">Old hunter Gehrman is an NPC that provides the Hunter with
    advise throughout the game, although very cryptic advice. He can be found sitting in his wheelchair
    around the Hunter\'s Dream. Gherman is one of the first Hunters, splitting from the Healing Church
    and forming the Black Church and the Hunters to eradicate the epidemic of beasts from Yharnam.
    It is believed that Gehrman was chosen by the Moon Presence as it\'s surrogate child from the
    description on the One Third Umbilical Cord found in the Old Abondoned Workshop.</string>
    <string name="gehrman_items">Items associated with Gehrman here</string>
    <string name="gehrman_quest_guide">Gherman provides the Hunter with the questline that is the
    entirety of Bloodborne. Although he did not task the Hunter with taking part in the hunt, he gives
    the hunter advice and encourages them to seek further answers of the nightmare throughout the game.
    Killing Gehrman at the and of the game is symbolic of the Hunter freeing him of the Moon Presence\'s
    grasp and allowing him to escape the Hunter\'s Nightmare.</string>

    <!-- Patches the Spider string set-->
    <string name="npc_patches">Patches the Spider</string>
    <string name="patches_description">Patches is a character that From Software enjoys using in all
    of their games to mess with the Hunter. His character is always a deceitful one looking to spark
    intrigue in the player with treasure to lure them into a trap. In Bloodborne he is a Spider with
    a man\'s head. Patches can be found in many areas of the game, depending on what phase the moon
    is on.</string>
    <string name="patches_items">After Patches has done his dirty work, the Hunter can confront him
    and receive the Beg for Life gesture. Selecting the "Not at all" dialogue option will reward the
    Hunter with the Anti Clockwise Metamorphosis rune. Killing Patches will reward the Hunter with
    some blood echoes and a Great One\'s Wisdom.</string>
    <string name="patches_quest_guide">Patches can be spoken with after killing Rom where the Young
    Girl was previously in Central Yharnam. Approaching him here will provide the player with the Tonsil
    Stone, a means to be sent to the Nightmare Frontier. Finding Patches in the nightmare Lecture Building
    will have Patches tell the Hunter that they are in his debt and should be thankful to him, and
    he will tell the Hunter to "throw themselves to the wolves". After falling for Patches\' trick, the
    Hunter can confront him once again by travelling through the lecture building 2nd floor and taking
    a ladder down into the room that he is hiding in. This will put Patches into a frightened state and
    he will try to convince the Hunter that he has done no wrong. There are several dialogue options
    available here, or he can be outright killed.</string>

    <!-- Provost Willem string set-->
    <string name="npc_willem">Provost Willem</string>
    <string name="willem_description">Willem is the leader of the Byrgenwerth institute, where the
    Healing Church was founded. Willem was one of those that deeply researched the Old Blood found in
    the Pthumerian Labyrinths underneath Yharnam. Willem\'s ultimate goal was to transcend humanity
    to it\'s next plane of thought. As time when on, Byrgenwerth was abandoned by many of the scholars
    to strive for differing goals. Willem is one of the few that remained loyal to the institute and
    researching a way to evolve humanity past it\'s limited self. Willem can be found on the balcony
    overlooking Lake Byrgenwerth.</string>
    <string name="willem_items">Speaking with Willem will grant the Hunter with two Insight. Killing
    him rewards the player with an Eye rune. </string>
    <string name="willem_quest_guide"></string>

    <!-- Retired Hunter Djura string set-->
    <string name="npc_djura">Retired Hunter Djura</string> <!-- Very tempting to type retarded hunter djura -->
    <string name="djura_description">Djura is the Hunter that is found in Old Yharnam. At first, he tells
    the Hunter to leave Old Yharnam and to leave the beasts be that live there as they mean no harm to those
    above. Entering Old Yharnam anyway will lead to Djura to fire his gatling gun at the Hunter. There is
    a way to get him to be friendly though(see quest guide)</string>
    <string name="djura_items">Killing Djura will grant the Hunter with the Power Keg Badge, allowing access
    to the Stake Driver, Rifle Spear, Oil Urns and Rope Molotovs from the messengers.</string>
    <string name="djura_quest_guide">To get Djura to become non-hostile, the Hunter must kill Darkbeast
    Paarl, and opening the great wooden doors closing Old Yharnam off from Yar\'Ghul. Afterwards,
    the Hunter must return to the Hunter\'s Dream, and travel back to the The Curch of the Good Chalice,
    or Graveyard of the Beast lanterns and finding their way to Djura without killing and of the beasts
    on their way. Speaking with Djura will give the Hunter the option to "spare the beasts". Doing so
    rewards the Hunter with the Powder Keg Badge and the Brush Off Dust gesture.</string>

    <!-- Valtr-->
    <string name="npc_valtr">Valtr</string>
    <string name="valtr_description">Valtr is an NPC that grants the Hunter access to the League covenant.
    Valtr can be found inside the windmill at the first lamp in the forbidden woods. It is said that Valtr
    and a group of his constables came to Yharnam chasing a Great Black Beast. All but Valtr died, who
    killed this beast and ate it\'s remains. This is how he came to his title of "Valtr, Beast Eater".</string>
    <string name="valtr_items">Joinging Valtr\'s covenant, The League, Valtr gives the player the
    Impurity rune. </string>
    <string name="valtr_quest_guide">Upon joining Valtr\'s covenant, the Hunter is rewarded with the
    Impurity rune. Killing one Vermin rewards the Hunter with a League Cane, and the League Oath.
    Killing five Vermin rewards the Hunter with the Master\'s Iron Helm, transition Valtr from being
    the leader of the covenant to the Hunter symbolically.</string>

    <!-- Young Girl and Older Sister-->
    <string name="npc_youngGirl_littleSister">Young Girl &amp; Little Sister</string>
    <string name="yg_ls_description">The Young Girl and later, her older sister can be found in Central
    Yharnam after travelling through the sewers and climbing all the way back up a ladder, leading
    to a shortcut as well. Which of the two sisters the Hunter will talk to depends on decisions
    made throughout the game. </string>
    <string name="yg_ls_items">The young girl will ask the Hunter to find her mother, Viola, who went on a
    search to find Father Gascoigne. Accepting the task will grant the Hunter with a Musical Box.</string>
    <string name="yg_ls_quest_guide">After killing Father Gascoigne and finding the Red Jeweled Broach, the
    Hunter can turn this item in to the Young Girl, prompting her to strike out and try to find her
    mother on her own. Returning to the Hunter\'s Dream, and killing the Giant Pig in the sewers
    will allow the hunter to find a Blood Soaked Ribbon. Loot this item and return to the Little Girl\'s
    home. Speaking to the window will now prompt dialogue from her older sister, who will ask if you
    have seen her little sister. Give her the Blood Soaked Ribbon, causing some rather disturbing dialogue.
    Returning to the Hunter\'s Dream and going back again, and traveling down the ladder will lead
    the Hunter to finding a White Messenger Ribbon, hinting that the older sister either fell off,
    or threw herself off the top of the ladder, ending the quest line and giving the Hunter a very
    depressing accessory to adorn the messengers with.</string>


</resources>